http://www.wokingfc.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Reminder: Spectators Code of Conduct - 6th December 2020
Season 20/21 - Supporters Return to Matches! - 1st December 2020
Purchase your #CardsLive ticket for Woking v Hartlepool - 10th December 2020
New Merchandise Has Arrived! - 10th December 2020
Tickets on sale to Silver Members - 10th December 2020
Fans return to the Laithwaite this Saturday - 9th December 2020
New Board Member - 9th December 2020
Cards Draw Dover In FA Trophy - 9th December 2020
Club Shop Opening Hours - 8th December 2020
Game Off: Altrincham v Woking - 8th December 2020
More News »
Vanarama
Woking Football Club, The Laithwaite Community Stadium, Kingfield, Woking, Surrey, GU22 9AA • 01483 772470
COVID-19 Information
At Woking Football Club, we are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of our supporters and visitors to our website.
Types of data we collect
Website Cookies
We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit www.aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance.
The list below describes the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.)
First Party Cookies
These are cookies that are set by this website directly.
Score Display: We use a cookie on our Fixtures & Results pages to allow you to choose how the score is displayed in the fixture list.
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.
You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
Third Party Cookies
These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site allowing visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by Twitter and Facebook. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. Cookies are also set by DAZN, the National League's Video Player provider, to enable targeted advertising. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website.
You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.
Mailing Lists
As part of the registration process for our email newsletter, we collect personal information. We use that information for a couple of reasons: to tell you about what’s going on at the football club, and to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information. We don’t rent or trade email lists with other organisations and businesses.
We use a third-party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our newsletter. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our newsletter. For more information, please see MailChimp’s privacy notice. You can unsubscribe to general mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails or by emailing dpofficer@wokingfc.co.uk
Online Voting & Contact Forms
When voting online, for example for Player of the Season or Goal of the Season, or when using one of our contact forms, your name, email address, and other relevant information will be stored in a secure password protected online database.
Offline Data
Personal data received in paper form, e.g. season ticket application forms or Woking News & Mail vouchers, will be held securely but only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which we have collected the data, at which point it is shredded. The payment section of any forms will be separated and shredded once the payment has been processed.
Sharing personal data
We may share your personal data with any service providers, sub-contractors and agents that we may appoint to perform functions on our behalf and in accordance with our instructions, including payment providers, email communication providers, IT service providers, accountants, auditors and lawyers.
Access to your personal information
You are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold. Please write to The Data Protection Officer, Woking Football Club, The Laithwaite Community Stadium, Kingfield, Woking, GU22 9AA.
Changes to this Privacy Notice
This policy will be reviewed every six months; it was last reviewed on 30th November 2020.
A company incorporated in England and Wales (company number: 03329172)
Registered office The Laithwaite Community Stadium, Kingfield, Woking, Surrey, GU22 9AA
Click here to read our Safeguarding Policy
Click here to read our Data Protection Privacy Policy
www.wokingfc.co.uk uses cookies. Some may have been set already. Click here to read about managing our cookies.
If you continue to use the site, we'll assume you're happy to accept the cookies.
